onnaway.com 2019-04-12

# OnnaWay.com | Real-Time Driver Tracking

## Privacy Policy

LAST MODIFIED: June 10, 2015

At OnnaWay, LLC., we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality and security of any personal information about our users. Your privacy is always at the top of our priorities, and we are focused on protecting it from unauthorized access. This Privacy & Security Policy supplements our Terms of Service and spells out how we collect, use, and disclose of information from or about you through our website OnnaWay.com and the OnnaWay service.

Users can access the OnnaWay service (the “Service”) via our website OnnaWay.com, applications on Devices, APIs, and third-parties. A “Device” is any device used to access the OnnaWay Service, including without limitation a computer, mobile phone, tablet, or other electronic device. By using our Service you are consenting to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy & Security Policy. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the OnnaWay client (“Client”) has engaged OnnaWay.

**The Information We Collect and Store**

OnnaWay employees are prohibited from viewing the content of the data you import into your OnnaWay account, except as provided in this Privacy & Security Policy. Of course, in the case that you request our help to resolve your support issues relating to that data, and only after receiving your permission, OnnaWay employees may access the relevant data.

We collect information primarily to provide better services to all of our customers. We collect information you provide us on our Sites such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, company name, credit card payment information and your customer and delivery information. We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect on our Sites.

When you visit our Sites, some information is automatically collected. This may include information such as the Operating System (OS) running on your device, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type, and language, and the website you visited before our Sites. We also collect information about how you use the Service.

We automatically collect information using “cookies” and Web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website and web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Sites or in our emails. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Sites, our marketing activities, and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Sites.

Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Sites and could remove cookies used for opt-out of tracking.

OnnaWay does not respond to “Do Not Track” browser signals or other mechanisms. Third parties may collect personal information about your online activities over time and across sites when you visit the Sites or use the OnnaWay Service.

OnnaWay retains your data while you are a customer and will delete your information within 12 months of either party’s termination of the Terms, upon written request.

**How We Use Information We Collect**

We use the information we collect primarily to provide, maintain, protect and improve our current products and to develop new ones. We use personal information collected through our Sites as described in this Policy or on our Sites. For example, we may use your information to:

  * Improve our services, Sites and how we operate our business;
  * Understand and enhance your experience using our Sites, products and services;
  * Provide and deliver products and services you request;
  * Respond to your comments or questions and for our Solutions team to provide service;
  * Send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * Communicate with you about promotions, upcoming events and news about products and services offered by OnnaWay and our selected partners;
  * Link or combine it with other information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
  * Protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized or illegal activity.

OnnaWay may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries. By using our services you consent to this transfer of your personal information.

Sharing of Personal Information

**Information You Share**

Our privacy policy does not cover any third party services. To learn about those third parties’ privacy practices, please visit their policies.

**Information Related to Data Collected through the OnnaWay Platform**

We collect information for our clients. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly. Access to Data Controlled by our Clients

OnnaWay has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct his query to the OnnaWay’s Client (the data controller). If the Client requests OnnaWay to remove the data, we will respond to the request within 30 business days.

**Data Retention**

OnnaWay will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. OnnaWay will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreement.

**Information We Share**

We do not share your personal information with third parties without your consent other than:

  * With third parties who work on our behalf provided such third parties enter into a written agreement with OnnaWay requiring that the third party provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the relevant Principles;
  * To comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process (provided that OnnaWay will endeavor to notify you if OnnaWay has received a lawful request for your information);
  * To protect the rights and property of OnnaWay, our agents, customers and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use;
  * In an emergency, including to protect the personal safety of any person; and
  * For the purposes of a business deal (or negotiation of a business deal) involving sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets (business deals may include, for example, any merger, financing, acquisition, divestiture or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding).

We may also share aggregate or deidentified information derived from your personal information.

**Personal Information Security**

OnnaWay takes reasonable steps to help protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. It is your responsibility to protect your user names and passwords to help prevent anyone from accessing or abusing your accounts and services. You should not use or reuse the same passwords you use with other accounts as your password for our services.

**Children**

If you are under 18, or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you reside, you may only use the OnnaWay website and OnnaWay Services with the consent of your parent or legal guardian.

**Your Information Choices and Changes**

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from OnnaWay by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your OnnaWay projects or our ongoing business relationship. You may also send requests about your contact preferences, changes and deletions to your information including requests to opt-out of sharing your personal information with third parties by emailing support@onnaway.com. OnnaWay will respond within ninety (90) days to any request to delete your information. Individuals who have provided information to OnnaWay’s customers must send requests to change or delete such information to the particular OnnaWay customer.

**Online Advertising We Use**

We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise OnnaWay across the Internet. AdWords remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the OnnaWay website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. **THIS COOKIE DOES NOT IN ANYWAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER.** The cookie is used to say "This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page." Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.

**How to Opt Out of Remarketing and Advertising.**

If you do not wish to participate in our Google AdWords Remarketing, you can opt out by visiting [Google's Ads Preferences Manager.](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated?hl=en)

**Changes to This Policy**

OnnaWay may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the “Last Updated” date above. You agree that your continued use of our Services after such changes have been published to our Services will constitute your acceptance of such revised Policy.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, you may contact us at by email at [support@onnaway.com](mailto:support@onnaway.com).
